A Guide to the Lester M. Salamon Papers FA1868
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Course Material, 1983-2017; 5; 2.28 Cubic Feet (6 containers)
  This series contains syllabi, copies of primary source documents, articles, and other course material used throughout Salamon's time teaching at John Hopkins University.
  - Politics of the Policy Process Course, Johns Hopkins University, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 368)
  - The Politics of the International Economic Policy Process Course, Georgetown University, 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 369)
  - The Policy Project Course, Johns Hopkins University, 2009-2011 (Box 44, Folder 370)
  - Various Nonprofit Course Syllabi, Johns Hopkins University, 2011-2012 (Box 44, Folder 371)
  - Tools of Public Action Course, Johns Hopkins University - Syllabi, 2004-2015 (Box 45, Folder 372-373)
  - Tools of Public Action Course, Johns Hopkins University - Short Memo Material, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 374)
  - Tools of Public Action Course, Johns Hopkins University - Quizzes, 2008-2014 (Box 45, Folder 375)
  - Tools of Public Action Course, Johns Hopkins University - Clippings, 2005-2008 (Box 45, Folder 376)
  - Tools of Public Action Course, Johns Hopkins University - Course Material/Contracting, undated (Box 45, Folder 377)
  - New Governance Course, Truman School of Public Affairs - Syllabi, undated (Box 45, Folder 378)
  - Tools of Government Course, Johns Hopkins University, 2004-2012 (Box 45, Folder 379)
  - The Nonprofit Sector: An Introduction Course, Johns Hopkins University, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 380)
  - Obamacare in Tools Perspective, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 381)
  - Healthcare Practicum Documents, 2013-2014 (Box 45, Folder 382)
  - Regulations on Corporate Accountability, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 383)
  - Pentagon Probes Suppliers' Hiring Following Boeing Scandal, Andy Pasztor, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 384)
  - Air Pollution Exemption, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 468)
  - Contracting Practicum, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 469)
  - Fracking, Hannah Wiseman, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 470)
  - Juvenile Mental Health Services, 2006-2007 (Box 56, Folder 471)
  - Regulation Practicum - Naural Gas, 2010-2011 (Box 56, Folder 472)
  - Transportation Grants Practicum, 2007-2011 (Box 56, Folder 473)
  - Tools Course Comments, 2009-2010 (Box 56, Folder 474)
  - Homeland Security Grants, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 475)
  - Capitation Grant Practicum, 2005-2007 (Box 56, Folder 476)
  - Regulatory Reform at OSHA, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 477)
  - OSHA Practicum, 1997-2010 (Box 56, Folder 478)
  - Medicaid Practicum, 2005-2010 (Box 57, Folder 479)
  - Federalization of Aviation Security, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 480)
  - Coal Tax Credit, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 481)
  - Medicare, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 482)
  - Tools of Government Course I - Notes, 2003-2017 (Box 88, Folder 866-867)
  - Tools of Government Course II - Notes, 2012-2017 (Box 88, Folder 868-870)
  - The Politics of the Policy Process, 1995 Fall (Box 89, Folder 872-873)
- Philanthropication thru Privatization (PtP) Project, 1999-2021; 6; 5.7 Cubic Feet (15 containers)
  This series contains information about Lester Salamon's Philanthropication thru Privataization (PtP) Project, funded by the Mott Foundation and made possible by cooperation with the East West Management Institute.
  - Proposals - Associazione di Fondazioni e di Casse di Risparmio Spa (ACRI) Award, 2009-2010 (Box 61, Folder 550)
  - Proposals - Ford Foundation, 2015 (Box 61, Folder 551)
  - Proposals - Various, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 552)
  - Proposals - Volkswagen, 2011-2012 (Box 61, Folder 553)
  - Proposals - Funder Letters, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 554)
  - Proposals - King Baudouin Foundation, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 555)
  - Proposals - Philanthropication thru Privatization: A New Route to Foundation Formation in Transitional Regions, 2010-2012 (Box 61, Folder 556)
  - Proposals - Mott Foundation, 2017 (Box 61, Folder 557)
  - Proposals - DEID Proposal, 2017 (Box 61, Folder 558)
  - Proposals - UBS, New Frontiers of Philanthropy, undated (Box 61, Folder 559)
  - Funder Reports - Finances, 2013-2014 (Box 61, Folder 560)
  - Funder Reports - FDI Uzbekistan Report, 2017 (Box 61, Folder 561)
  - Funder Reports - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 61, Folder 562)
  - Flyers, undated (Box 61, Folder 563)
  - Powerpoint Presentations, 2016 (Box 61, Folder 564)
  - Conferences - Hanover, 2016 (Box 61, Folder 565)
  - Conferences - Erste Stiftung Case Study, 2010 (Box 61, Folder 566)
  - Conferences - Expenses, 2010-2013 (Box 61, Folder 567)
  - Conferences - Concept Note, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 568)
  - Conferences - Finances, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 569)
  - Conferences - Associate Letter, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 570)
  - Conferences - Pending, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 571)
  - State Owned Entities, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 572)
  - Government Controlled Revenue Streams - Mining, 2018 (Box 62, Folder 573)
  - Pelosi, How-To Extractives, 2016 (Box 62, Folder 574)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - How-To Stolen Assets, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 575)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Session Penalty Payments Order, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 576)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Open Society Initiative Seminar, 2016 (Box 62, Folder 577)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Global Forum on Asset Recovery (GFAR), 2017 (Box 62, Folder 578)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Clippings, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 579)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Swiss Experience in Returning Illicit Assets, undated (Box 62, Folder 580)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Nigeria Experience on Asset Recovery, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 581)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - La Caxia Bank Foundation, 2012 (Box 62, Folder 582)
  - Stolen/Stranded Assets - Corruption, Latin America, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 583)
  - Case Studies - Brazil, 2017-2018 (Box 62, Folder 584)
  - Case Studies - Penalty-Based Foundation, undated (Box 62, Folder 585)
  - ERSTE Foundation, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 687)
  - Privatization, Wikipedia, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 690)
  - Mott Foundation Report, 2008-2009 (Box 68, Folder 691)
  - Discovery - Latin America, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 692)
  - Case Study Associates Meeting, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 693)
  - Project Summary Sheets, undated (Box 68, Folder 694)
  - Privatization Barometer, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 695)
  - World Bank, 2010 (Box 69, Folder 707)
  - Discovery Field Guide, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 708)
  - Discovery Associations, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 709)
  - Turin, Italy Meeting, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 710)
  - Case Studies, undated (Box 69, Folder 711)
  - ACRI Report, Year 1, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 716)
  - DLA Piper, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 717)
  - Czech Republic, 2000-2005 (Box 70, Folder 718)
  - Clippings and Notes, 2005-2007 (Box 70, Folder 719)
  - Privatization Barometer Article, 2007-2009 (Box 70, Folder 720)
  - Privatization Barometer, 2011-2012 (Box 70, Folder 721)
  - Community Trusts Case Study, undated (Box 70, Folder 722)
  - Case Studies, undated (Box 70, Folder 723)
  - India - Jasmeet Bawa, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 724)
  - Borrowing and Debt, Yetman, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 725)
  - The International Experience with Privatization, Nellis, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 726)
  - Turkey, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 727)
  - Brochure, undated (Box 71, Folder 728)
  - Case Study Agreements, 2010 (Box 71, Folder 729)
  - Executive Summary, 2014 (Box 71, Folder 730)
  - Debt Swaps - Greece, 2009-2015 (Box 71, Folder 731)
  - Debt Swaps - International Foundation Directory, 2015 (Box 71, Folder 732)
  - Stolen Assets - Stranded Assets Documents, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 733)
  - Stolen Assets - World Bank Report, 2013-2015 (Box 71, Folder 734)
  - Foundations for Extracting, International Finance Corporation (IFC) Report, 2015 (Box 71, Folder 735)
  - Extractive Industries and Foundations, 2011-2015 (Box 71, Folder 736)
  - Asset Building for Social Change, Ford Foundation, undated (Box 71, Folder 737)
  - Kyrgyzstan Nonprofit Law, 1999-2015 (Box 71, Folder 738)
  - Measuring Civil Society and Volunteering, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 739)
  - Kyrgyzstan, 2015 (Box 71, Folder 740)
  - Implications for the Mining Industry, 2016 (Box 71, Folder 741)
  - Exposure Draft, undated (Box 77, Folder 798)
  - La Caixa Banking Foundation Case Study, 2017-2019 (Box 79, Folder 812-813)
  - Binder, 2008-2009 (Box 81, Folder 826-827)
  - Summary Case Study Reports, 2013 (Box 87, Folder 862)
  - Case Studies and How-To Booklets, 2019-2020 (Box 87, Folder 863)
  - Implementation, 2019-2021 (Box 90, Folder 880)
  - Compilations, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 913-914)
  - Case Studies, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 915-916)
  - Discovery Phase - Past PtP Cases, 2001-2010 (Box 97, Folder 917-918)
  - Philanthropication thru Privatization (PtP) and Stolen Assets Flyers, 2019 (Box 104, Folder 1002)
  - Philanthropication thru Privatization Flyers, 2018-2019 (Box 104, Folder 1003)
  - USAID and Data.org PtP Proposals, 2019-2020 (Box 133, Folder 1461)
  - Dissemination, 2009-2010 (Box 133, Folder 1473)
  - Maryland and United States, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 1478)
  - Ford Report, 2020 (Box 133, Folder 1483)
- Pilot Projects, 2001-2018; 7; 1.9 Cubic Feet (5 containers)
  These items were designated as "pilot projects" by Lester Salamon. Most of the projects within this series evolved into larger projects and related material can be found within other series.
  - Uzbekistan, 2014-2017 (Box 62, Folder 586)
  - Uzbekistan - Mahalla Institution in Uzbekistan: Historical Experience and Today's Life, undated (Box 62, Folder 586)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Uzbekistan - From a Strong State to a Strong Civil Society (Mahalla: Historical Experience and Modern Times), undated (Box 62, Folder 586)
  - Uzbekistan Reform Process, 2018 (Box 62, Folder 587)
  - Uzbekistan, 2017 (Box 62, Folder 588)
  - Central Asia Economic Outlook, 2018 (Box 62, Folder 589)
  - IMF Materials on Uzbekistan Economy, 2018 (Box 62, Folder 590)
  - World Bank Materials on FDI, undated (Box 62, Folder 591)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Production, 2013-2014 (Box 63, Folder 592)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 593)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Audience Engagement, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 594)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Omidyar Correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 63, Folder 595)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy, 2007-2008 (Box 63, Folder 596)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Prospectus, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 597)
  - Kresge Foundation, Detroit, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 598)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Kresge Foundation, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 599)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Funders, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 600)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Proposals, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 601)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Actors, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 602)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Glossary, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 603)
  - VolunteerMatch Offering, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 604)
  - Loan Funds, Julia Sass-Rubin, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 605)
  - Secondary Markets, Bill Burckart, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 606)
  - Secondary Market for Community Development Loans, Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 607)
  - Sims Capital, 2006-2009 (Box 63, Folder 608)
  - Mission Related Investing, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 609)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Rating Agencies, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 610)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Insurance, Jonathan Morduch, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 611)
  - Barter Arrangements, undated (Box 64, Folder 612)
  - Disrupting Philanthropy: Technology and the Future of the Social Sector, Lucy Bernholz, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 613)
  - Capacity Builders, undated (Box 64, Folder 614)
  - Philanthropic Advisors Group, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 615)
  - Understanding Social Enterprise, Janelle Kerlin, undated (Box 64, Folder 616)
  - New Philanthropic Funds, undated (Box 64, Folder 617)
  - Advanced Market Commitment, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 618)
  - Social Impact Bonds, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 619)
  - Charter School Finance, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 620)
  - Global Impact Investing Network (GIIN), 2009 (Box 64, Folder 621)
  - Equity Advancing Equity, Richter and Bernholtz, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 622)
  - Equity Funds, 2009-2012 (Box 64, Folder 623)
  - Charter School Financing Gates Guarantee, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 624)
  - Monitor Report Impact Investing, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 625)
  - Crowd Sourcing Clippings, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 626)
  - GIIRS Company Assessment, 2013 (Box 64, Folder 627)
  - Accelerating Impact, Impact Investing, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 628)
  - Capital Ideas: Moving from Short-Term Engagement to Long-Term Sustainability, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 629)
  - Compounding Impact, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 630)
  - Funder's Guide to Investing, Cooch and Kramer, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 631)
  - The Social Investment Bank, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 632)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Overview, undated (Box 65, Folder 633)
  - Too Important to Fail: The Impact of Community Development Banking Institutions, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 634)
  - Nonprofit Capital: A Review of Problems and Strategies, William Ryan, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 635)
  - Two Trillion and Counting: Assessing the Credit Gap for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises in the Developing World, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 636)
  - Access to Capital: A Briefing Paper, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 637)
  - U.S. Financial Assets Statistics, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 638)
  - World Economic Forum, Blended Value Investing, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 639)
  - Mobilizing Private Capital for Public Good, Canadian Task Force on Social Finance, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 640)
  - Creating an Ethical Stock Exchange, Jamie Hartzell, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 641)
  - The Next 4 Billion: Market Size and Business Strategy at the Base of the Pyramid, Hammond, Kramer, et. al, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 642)
  - The Secondary Market for Community Development Loans, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 643)
  - Calvert Foundation, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 644)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Kellogg Foundation Proposal, 2006-2011 (Box 65, Folder 645)
  - Analysis of Compounding impact, Bill Burckart, 2007-2008 (Box 65, Folder 646)
  - Heron Foundation Strategy (Clara Miller), 2012 (Box 65, Folder 647)
  - Heron Foundation, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 648)
  - Revisiting the CRA: Perspectives on the Future of the Community Reinvestment Act, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 649)
  - Program-Related Investing, 2006-2010 (Box 66, Folder 650)
  - Community Development Investment Review, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 651)
  - Impact Investing, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 652)
  - Sustainable Investing, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 653)
  - Social Enterprise: From Definitions to Developments in Practice, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 654)
  - Strategies for Foundations: When, Why, and How to Use Venture Philanthropy, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 655)
  - A Guide to Venture Philanthropy: For Venture Capital and Private Equity Investors, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 656)
  - Fondazione CRT, undated (Box 66, Folder 657)
  - Catalytic Philanthropy, Mark R. Kramer, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 658)
  - History of PRIs, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 659)
  - Foundation Center PRIs, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 660)
  - FSG Law of Mission Investing, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 661)
  - Foundation Center Yearbook, 2011-2013 (Box 66, Folder 662)
  - Heron Foundation - Mission Related Investing, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 663)
  - Mission Investing in Climate Change, Mark Kramer, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 664)
  - Germany, Social Investment Manual, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 665)
  - Foundation Center Mission Investing, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 666)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Training Webinars, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 667)
  - Mission Investing by U.S. Foundations, Cooch and Kramer, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 668)
- Related Projects, 1967-2021; 8; 25.25 Cubic Feet (67 containers)
  This series contains background information, correspondence, and drafts relating to Salamon's many projects, books, and articles.
  - Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA), 2000-2008 (Box 67, Folder 669)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - State Department, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 670)
  - White House Pay For Success Conference, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 671)
  - Impact Measurement, Federal Reserve Session, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 672)
  - Social Enterprise Alliance Project, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 673)
  - Measuring Performance: Obama Initiatives, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 674)
  - Keystone: Bonbright, 2010 (Box 67, Folder 675)
  - Impact Reporting and Investment Standards (IRIS)/GINN Project, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 676)
  - Scope of U.S. Social Enterprise, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 677)
  - Case for Community Philanthropy, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 678)
  - Association for Enterprise Opportunity (AEO) - Johns Hopkins University Partnership, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 679)
  - Association for Enterprise Opportunity (AEO) - New Frontiers Proposal, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 680)
  - Burckart Agreements, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 681)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Tracking, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 682)
  - NESST Proposals, undated (Box 67, Folder 683)
  - Net Impact Conference, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 684)
  - NIP Finance Workshop, White House, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 685)
  - Emily Barman, 2016-2017 (Box 67, Folder 686)
  - Consumers Union Nonprofit Conversions, Protecting the Community's Health Assets (Box 68)
  - Italian Bank Foundations, 1998-2010 (Box 68, Folder 689)
  - Once Foundation, Spain, undated (Box 68, Folder 696)
  - Association of Charitable Foundations - Governance of Foundations, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 697)
  - Protecting Health, Preserving Assets: A Comprehensive Study of Laws Governing Conversions, Mergers, and Acquisitions Among Health Care Entities, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 698)
  - Capitalizing the Sweet Spot, Nonprofit Finance Fund, undated (Box 68, Folder 699)
  - New Foundations in Health: Six Stories, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 700)
  - Privatization Governance and Public Management: The Challenges Ahead, Dennis A. Rondinelli, undated (Box 69, Folder 701)
  - Multinational Strategic Alliances and Acquisitions in Central and Eastern Europe, Rondinelli and Black, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 702)
  - The Dynamics of Privatization During Economic Adjustment, Rondinelli and Priebjrivat, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 703)
  - Permanent University Fund, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 704)
  - New Zealand Community Trusts, 2002-2008 (Box 69, Folder 705-706)
  - Consumer Union Building Foundations, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 712)
  - Polish-American Freedom Foundation, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 713)
  - Conversion Foundations, Healthcare Conversions, 2000-2009 (Box 70, Folder 714)
  - Social Housing and Sustainable Communities, 2009-2013 (Box 70, Folder 715)
  - Newmont Ahafo Development Foundation (NADeF), 2014 (Box 72, Folder 742)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Commission for a Healthier America, 2013 (Box 72, Folder 743)
  - Philanthropic Banks Revisions, 2010-2013 (Box 72, Folder 744)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Hewlett Foundation, 2012-2013 (Box 72, Folder 745)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Finalization, undated (Box 72, Folder 746)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Overview, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 747)
  - Social Accountability Report, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 748)
  - Conversion Foundations, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 749)
  - U.S. Conversion Foundations, Consumers Union, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 750)
  - Private Capital, Public Good Report, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 751)
  - G8 Impact Investment Report, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 752)
  - Investing for Global Impact, 2014-2015 (Box 72, Folder 753)
  - World Investment Report, United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) Summary, undated (Box 72, Folder 754)
  - Social Accountability, World Bank Global Partnership for Social Accountability (GPSA) Workshop, 2014 (Box 73, Folder 755)
  - World Bank Sustainability, 2011-2013 (Box 73, Folder 756)
  - Global Impact Investing Network (GIIN) Impact Investing Trends, 2016 (Box 73, Folder 757)
  - De-Politicizing the Western Lands Issue, 2015-2016 (Box 73, Folder 758)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Speech, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 759)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Flyers, undated (Box 73, Folder 760)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - The Revolution in Social Purpose Finance Speech, 2014 (Box 73, Folder 761)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - TPW West Annual Meeting Speech, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 762)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Vignettes, 2011-2012 (Box 73, Folder 763)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Capital Aggregators, 2011-2012 (Box 73, Folder 764)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Secondary Markets, Erickson, 2012 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Social Stock Exchanges, Shahnaz-Kraubill, 2009-2012 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Foundations as Philanthropic Banks, 2012 (Box 74, Folder 767)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Corporate-Originated Charitable Funds, 2011-2012 (Box 74, Folder 768)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Enterprise Brokers, Wood-Hagerman, 2012 (Box 74, Folder 769)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Capacity Builders, Tuan, 2010-2012 (Box 74, Folder 770)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Online Portals and Exchanges, Stehle, 2011-2012 (Box 74, Folder 771)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Funding Collaboratives, Eikenberry-Bearman, 2009-2012 (Box 74, Folder 772)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Hagerman, 2010-2011 (Box 74, Folder 773)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Quasi-Public Social Investment Funds, 2011 (Box 74, Folder 774)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Tools Introduction Chapter, Ragin, 2012 (Box 74, Folder 775)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Loans/Loan Guarantees, Miller, 2011-2012 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Equity Investments, 2010-2012 (Box 74, Folder 777)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Bonds, Berenbach, 2011-2012 (Box 75, Folder 778)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Securitization, 2011-2012 (Box 75, Folder 779)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Equity Investments, Brand-Kohler, 2012-2013 (Box 75, Folder 780)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Social Impact Bonds, Von Glahn, 2012-2013 (Box 75, Folder 781)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Insurance, 2007-2012 (Box 75, Folder 782)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Grants, Frumkin, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 783)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Socially Responsible Investment, 2011-2012 (Box 75, Folder 784)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Who Gains, Who Loses?, Edwards, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 785)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Who Gains?, Bishop-Green, 2011-2013 (Box 75, Folder 786)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Demand Side of the Social Investment Marketplace, Nichols, 2011-2012 (Box 76, Folder 787)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Elusive Quest for Impact, Trelstad, 2011-2012 (Box 76, Folder 788)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - A Policy Agenda, Sagawa, 2011-2012 (Box 76, Folder 789)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - A Global Perspective, Martin, 2011 (Box 76, Folder 790)
  - Implementing the New United Nations Handbook on Nonprofit Institutions in Latin America, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 794)
  - Community Foundation of the Chesapeake, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 795)
  - Global Volunteering Overview and FAQ, undated (Box 76, Folder 796)
  - The Listening Post Project, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 797)
  - RDI Survey Frequencies, undated (Box 77, Folder 802)
  - Aspen Institute Nonprofit Strategy Group - Advocacy and Civic Participation Session, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 803)
  - National Nonprofit Book - The Invisible Sector - RDI Data, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 804-805)
  - National Nonprofit Book - Drafts, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 806)
  - National Nonprofit Book - RDI and II, undated (Box 78, Folder 807)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Sector Project - The Emerging Sector Revisited, 1998-1999 (Box 78, Folder 808)
  - Leverage for Good: An Introduction to the New Frontiers of Philanthropy and Social Investment, 2014 (Box 79, Folder 809)